* OFFER

Jestes w: [Home](https://www.revas.online/en "Revas Business Simulation Games")1 \- Privacy policy

Privacy policy
==============

**Revas Sp. z o.o. \[limited liability company\] (hereafter: Revas)** as a service provider in the education sector, considers protection of personal data to be one of the most important aspects of its activity. Therefore, our goal is to duly inform our Users about matters related to the protection of personal data and its processing.

The personal data Controller
----------------------------

Revas Spółka z o.o. with a registered office in Rzeszów  
at Wrzesława Romańczuka 3,  
35-302 Rzeszów.  
KRS: 0000638640, NIP: 5170376971, REGON: 365460300  
e-mail: [kontakt@revas.pl](mailto: kontakt@revas.pl)

What does personal data actually mean?
--------------------------------------

Personal data – it means any information allowing to identify a natural person. It may contain data such as: name and surname, identification number, location data, online identification number, but also one or several specific factors determining the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of a natural person.

The processing of personal data is any activity related to it, e.g. collection, storage, recording, dissemination or otherwise making available, use, erasure or destruction of personal data.

Purposes and legal basis for personal data processing
-----------------------------------------------------

Your personal data may be processed for the following purposes:

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **If you…** | **Personal data** | **Source of data** | **Legal basis** |
| **visit our website** | Visiting the website starts an automatic collection of the technical data about the User’s visit, e.g. IP address, domain name, browser type, operating system, etc. | We process personal data collected by cookies. More information about cookies and the data they collect can be found at the bottom of the website. | article 6 sec. 1 of the GDPR – legitimate interest of the controller |
| **subscribed to our newsletter** | The newsletter service requires providing data such as: name, e-mail address. We can also use the function of checking if the correspondence sent to you was opened, as well as the function of collecting information about the messages you click, both to match in order to best match the content to your interests. | We collect the data directly from you when you fill out the newsletter form and use cookies. | article 6 sec. 1 of the GDPR – zgoda na przetwarzanie danych |
| **want to contact us through the contact form** | The data contained in the contact form: name, surname, e-mail address will be processed in order to answer the question or price inquiry. | We obtain data directly from you when you contact us through e-mail, telephone or traditional post. | article 6 sec. 1 of the GDPR – legitimate interest of the controller |
| **want to know the price of our simulations** | The data contained in the contact form: name, surname, e-mail address, institution will be processed in order to answer the price inquiry. | We obtain the data directly from you when you contact us through the website. | article 6 sec. 1 of the GDPR – |
| **Follow or comment our Facebook/Instagram/ LinkedIn/Twitter fanpage** | We process the data contained on social media if you: follow, comment or react to the content on our fanpage. | Facebook and Instagram (Meta Platform Ireland Ltd) is the joint controller of the personal data of the portal users, the data is obtained directly from the portal. | article 6 sec. 1 of the GDPR – legitimate interest of the controller |
| **use our training services** | We collect data of trainees, persons representing entities and concluding contracts in order to organize training, issue certificates and perform the concluded contract. | In order to provide our services, we conclude a contract which authorizes us to process the data. | article 6 sec. 1 of the GDPR – performance of the contract |
| **use our Business Simulation Games** | We process personal data, e-mail address, place of work/school of the student, telephone number. | We process the data provided by users in the registration form in order to perform the contract concluded with the entity / school/institution that purchased a license for the software from us. | article 6 sec. 1 of the GDPR – performance of the contract |

Recipients of personal data
---------------------------

Personal data may be shared with entities providing services to us – that is legal services, accounting services, IT services, marketing services, advertising services, logistics and postal services – to the extent necessary to provide services.

The right of access to data and User rights
-------------------------------------------

According to the GDPR, every User, depending on the purposes and legal basis on which the personal data was collected, has the following rights:

1. Right of access to data (Article 15 of the GDPR)
2. Right to rectification (Article 16 of the GDPR)
3. Right to erasure (“right to be forgotten”) (Article 17 of the GDPR)
4. Right to restriction of processing (Article 18 of the GDPR)
5. Right to object (Article 21 of the GDPR)

In regard to services provided in social media, you can also exercise your rights directly against:

* [Facebook’a](https://pl-pl.facebook.com/privacy/explanation/) (Meta Platforms Ireland Ltd.)
* [Instagram](https://help.instagram.com/519522125107875/?maybe_redirect_pol=0) (Meta Platforms Ireland Ltd.)
* [Twitter](https://twitter.com/en/privacy) (Twitter, Inc.)
* [LinkedIn](https://pl.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy) (LinkedIn Ireland Unlimited Company)

If you believe that the processing of personal data violates the law, you have also the right to lodge a complaint with the President of the Office for Personal Data Protection.

How long do we process personal data ?
--------------------------------------

* for the duration of the license’s contract– in relation to personal data of Business Simulation Games’ users;
* for the period required by tax law – in relation to personal data associated with the fulfilment of obligations under tax law;
* until an effective objection has been lodged – in relation to personal data processed on the basis of the legitimate interest of the Controller or for marketing purposes;
* until the consent is withdrawn or the purpose of processing is achieved – in relation to personal data processed on the basis of consent;
* until they become outdated or lose their usefulness – in relation to personal data processed mainly for analytical and statistical purposes, the use of cookies and administration of the Controller’s pages.

Safeguards
----------

Our website employs safety measures in order to protect all personal data remaining under control of our Controller against loss, unauthorised processing and alteration. The Controller has also implemented an internal Personal Data Protection Policy in order to ensure the personal data are adequately protected in accordance with the applicable rules and norms and in particular:

1. Only authorized employees or associates of the Controller have direct access to personal data collected by the Controller,
2. The Controller represents that by commissioning other entities to provide services, he/she requires maintenance of adequately high standards for the protection of personal data, signing of relevant entrustment contracts, in which the partners confirm the application of the standards and the right to audit the compliance of their activities with these standards,
3. The Controller applies a high level of security, including cryptographic protection for the transmission of personal data (the SSL protocol),
4. Due to the public nature of the Internet, the use of services provided by electronic means may entail certain risks, regardless of due diligence exercised by the Controller.

How do we use the information obtained?
---------------------------------------

### Providing, improving and developing our services.

The availability of this information allows us to maintain the Services, personalize the content and suggest various solutions to Users, because our understanding of how users use elements of the services and resources that are of interest to them is contingent upon the information collected. We also use the information we collect to offer various types of facilitations and suggestions.

### Display and monitoring of ads and services

We use the information we have available to improve our advertising and measuring systems which, in turn, is intended to display ads that are of interest to the User, both within and outside the website, as well as to measure the effectiveness and scope – of both ads and services.

### Cookies (and other similar technologies) Policy

Cookies are small text files stored on the User’s computer or other mobile device when they use the websites. These files are used, among others, for various functions provided on the website or to confirm whether the User has seen a specific content from the given website.

1. In relation to providing the content of websites, we use the so-called cookies.
2. When entering the Website for the first time, you may consent to our cookies or take other actions indicated in the message in order to be able to continue using the Website. By using the Website, you consent, if you do not consent – leave the Website.
3. You can change your browser’s settings, disable or delete cookies. In the “help” tab in your browser you will find instructions about how to do this.
4. Disabling or changing cookie settings may affect some of the functionalities of the website.
5. Lack of changes in the settings means you consent to the use of cookies.

We use two cookies types:

1. performance cookies (they collect information such as the way visitors use the website, the most visited pages, error messages, etc.),
2. functional cookies (save user settings, language, consents, etc.), such as:
    * Google Analytics – they are used to analyze and measure how users use our services. You will find more information about the Google Analytics service here: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy),
    * Facebook – they are used to analyze and measure how users use our services. You will find more information about the Facebook service here: [https://pl-pl.facebook.com/privacy/explanation/](https://pl-pl.facebook.com/privacy/explanation/),
    * Session cookies – these are temporary pieces of information stored in the browser’s memory until the end of the session, i.e. closing it.

### Information contained in access logs

Similarly to most of Internet services publishers, we collect information about the use of the websites by users and their IP addresses, based on the analysis of access logs. This information is used for technical purposes related to the administration of the servers of our websites, as well as for statistical purposes, for the demographic analysis of users.

How to contact us?
------------------

If you have any questions or concerns about how we process personal data, you can contact us through:  
e-mail: [rodo@revas.pl](mailto:rodo@revas.pl)  
by post: Revas sp. z o.o.  
ul. Wrzesława Romańczuka 3  
35-302 Rzeszów  
Poland

Amendments to the Privacy Policy
--------------------------------

The Privacy Policy can be amended. The most current version of the Policy will govern our use of information and such version will always be available at.  
[https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy](https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy).

Revas sp. z o.o.

ul. Wrzesława Romańczuka 3

35-302 Rzeszów

Poland

© 2024 Revas. All Rights Reserved.

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Settings Accept [Read More](https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy/)

Privacy & Cookies Policy

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

**Functional cookies**  
You cannot disable these cookies because they are necessary for our site to work properly.  
  
**Social features**  
Our website has plugins of social networking websites that can use cookies. If you do not agree to their use, just refrain from using these functions. Remember that you can always manage your privacy settings from your social media accounts.

SAVE & ACCEPT

* ##### Leave your contact details and we will set up an online meeting with a simulation expert.

* name \*
    
* email\_address \*
    
* This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms?hl=en) apply.
    
* agreePrivatePolicy \*
    
     \* I agree to the processing of my personal data by REVAS Sp. z o.o. based in Rzeszów to contact me at my request in order to get more information about the simulations and their pricing [Privacy Policy](https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy/). I know that consent is voluntary.
    
     *     

×

Leave us your contact details  
and we will send you the pricing structure

* name \*
    
* email\_address \*
    
* institution \*
    
* This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms?hl=en) apply.
    
* agreePrivatePolicy \*
    
     \* I agree to the processing of my personal data by REVAS Sp. z o.o. based in Rzeszów to contact me at my request in order to get more information about the simulations and their pricing [Privacy Policy](https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy/). I know that consent is voluntary.
    
     *     

Or, if you don’t want to wait…  
call us!

Ela and Marzena will gladly  
answer all your questions.

Ela Szczepaniak

t.[(48) 502 148 260](tel:+48502148260)

Marzena Karpiak

t.[(48) 536 488 306](tel:+48536488306)

X

Leave us your contact details  
and we will send you the pricing structure

* name \*
    
* email\_address \*
    
* institution \*
    
* This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms?hl=en) apply.
    
* agreePrivatePolicy \*
    
     \* I agree to the processing of my personal data by REVAS Sp. z o.o. based in Rzeszów to contact me at my request in order to get more information about the simulations and their pricing [Privacy Policy](https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy/). I know that consent is voluntary.
    
     *     

Or, if you don’t want to wait…  
call us!

Ela and Marzena will gladly  
answer all your questions.

Ela Szczepaniak

t.[(48) 502 148 260](tel:+48502148260)

Marzena Karpiak

t.[(48) 536 488 306](tel:+48536488306)

X

Take a look inside

Choose a game

Choose the industry that you want to see. You will be automatically transferred to an advanced, previously prepared game

* * *

[  
See  
Car repair shop](https://demo-games.revas.online/demo/mechanik_en_6/return-url)

[  
See  
Hair salon](https://demo-games.revas.online/demo/hairdressing/return-url)

[  
See  
IT services](https://demo-games.revas.online/demo/itservice_en_5/return-url)

[  
See  
Travel agency](https://demo-games.revas.online/demo/travel_en/return-url)

[  
See  
Beauty salon](https://demo-games.revas.online/demo/beauty/return-url)

[  
See  
Event agency](https://demo-games.revas.online/demo/event_en_6/return-url)

×

Choose a simulation
-------------------

X

We are available online from Monday to Friday, from 8 am to 4 pm (CEST). You can contact us through an email or through Live Chat. We will reply as soon as possible 🙂  

Phone number

\* I agree to the processing of my personal data by REVAS Sp. z o.o. based in Rzeszów to contact me at my request in accordance with [Privacy Policy](https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy/).

×

We loved the opportunity to apply our business knowledge in a real world context. By analyzing our results from previous rounds, we have learned to maximize our profits as well as how to take care of customer and employee satisfaction. It was great how realistic the simulation was and how many variables were taken into account.

Jakub Lal

Student  
University of Information Technology and Management in Rzeszow

×

The game itself is very well developed keeping in mind the work-from-home nature that pre-exists in current times. While some can pass it off as just a game, the insight attained from it is invaluable, especially when money is a constraint as it very much is in the real world and failure is not an option. Everything in the simulation is in the right place and the progression of the levels make logical sense even in a virtual scenario. We highly appreciated the fact that the game catered to ALL the scenarios that concern a business; financial, strategy, marketing, human resources and even supply chain to a limited extent.

Rhys Pereira

Student  
EDHEC Business School

×

I thought the „Electronic Store“ simulation would be great to implement during the processes of onboarding and training of new entry level employees who haven’t had any experience in the given field. It was great helping everyone with their decisions and how invested they all became in the game. Some players stuck to one strategy that proved to be successful, while others decided to experiment. Given the fact everyone was competing against each other in the same market, the players had to study their competition’s strategies and try to think one that would help their business grow. Every round was different and exciting. I would definitely recommend this simulation, or any other simulation by Revas, for education or training of employees. It has been a great pleasure to work with the Revas team and I hope we will work together again in the near future.

Ivana Maja Milicevic

Human Resources Associate  
M SAN Grupa

×

I think Revas Business Simulation Games gives a fantastic opportunity for youngsters to apply all the concepts that they are learning or have learnt in their classrooms. We as teachers talk about real life situations and try to give students a feel through case studies. This, however, is way beyond any of that! My students’ understanding of the concepts has improved so much. Thank you Revas!

Dhanya Seshan

IBDP Business Management Facilitator  
International School of Budapest

×

Did you like what you saw?

Marzena Karpiak

×

### Szkolne Mistrzostwa Menedżerskie

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis.

Liczba uczestników: 100Symulacja: Biuro podróży

×

### Wirtualny Menedżer

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis.

Liczba uczestników: 100Symulacja: Biuro podróży

×

### Konkurs Manager Roku

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis.

Liczba uczestników: 100Symulacja: Biuro podróży

×

### Podkarpackie Mistrzostwa Przedsiębiorczości Społecznej

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis.

Liczba uczestników: 100Symulacja: Biuro podróży

×

### Pomorskie Mistrzostwa Wirtualnej Przedsiębiorczości

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis.

Liczba uczestników: 100Symulacja: Biuro podróży

×

### Rozgrywki o Puchar Rektora UP

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis.

Liczba uczestników: 100Symulacja: Biuro podróży

×

### Mieleckie Mistrzostwa Menedżerskie

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis.

Liczba uczestników: 100Symulacja: Biuro podróży

×

### Rzeszowskie Mistrzostwa Menedżerskie

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis.

Liczba uczestników: 100Symulacja: Biuro podróży

×

### Warszawskie Mistrzostwa Startup Jump

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Quis ipsum suspendisse ultrices gravida. Risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan lacus vel facilisis.

Liczba uczestników: 100Symulacja: Biuro podróży

×

Watch the video

×

Need more information?

We are glad that you want to get more familiar with the simulations! Use the contact form to schedule a presentation. Choose your time zone here and we will contact you as soon as possible to find a suitable date and form of the meeting.

Name and surname\*

E-mail\*

Phone number\*

Time zone\*Choose your time zone(UTC-11:00) Midway(UTC-11:00) Niue(UTC-11:00) Pago\_Pago(UTC-10:00) Honolulu(UTC-10:00) Rarotonga(UTC-10:00) Tahiti(UTC-09:00) Adak(UTC-09:30) Marquesas(UTC-09:00) Gambier(UTC-08:00) Anchorage(UTC-08:00) Juneau(UTC-08:00) Metlakatla(UTC-08:00) Nome(UTC-08:00) Pitcairn(UTC-08:00) Sitka(UTC-08:00) Yakutat(UTC-07:00) Creston(UTC-07:00) Dawson(UTC-07:00) Dawson\_Creek(UTC-07:00) Fort\_Nelson(UTC-07:00) Hermosillo(UTC-07:00) Los\_Angeles(UTC-07:00) Phoenix(UTC-07:00) Tijuana(UTC-07:00) Vancouver(UTC-07:00) Whitehorse(UTC-06:00) Belize(UTC-06:00) Boise(UTC-06:00) Cambridge\_Bay(UTC-06:00) Chihuahua(UTC-06:00) Costa\_Rica(UTC-06:00) Denver(UTC-06:00) Easter(UTC-06:00) Edmonton(UTC-06:00) El\_Salvador(UTC-06:00) Galapagos(UTC-06:00) Guatemala(UTC-06:00) Inuvik(UTC-06:00) Managua(UTC-06:00) Mazatlan(UTC-06:00) Ojinaga(UTC-06:00) Regina(UTC-06:00) Swift\_Current(UTC-06:00) Tegucigalpa(UTC-06:00) Yellowknife(UTC-05:00) Atikokan(UTC-05:00) Bahia\_Banderas(UTC-05:00) Beulah(UTC-05:00) Bogota(UTC-05:00) Cancun(UTC-05:00) Cayman(UTC-05:00) Center(UTC-05:00) Chicago(UTC-05:00) Eirunepe(UTC-05:00) Guayaquil(UTC-05:00) Jamaica(UTC-05:00) Knox(UTC-05:00) Lima(UTC-05:00) Matamoros(UTC-05:00) Menominee(UTC-05:00) Merida(UTC-05:00) Mexico\_City(UTC-05:00) Monterrey(UTC-05:00) New\_Salem(UTC-05:00) Panama(UTC-05:00) Rainy\_River(UTC-05:00) Rankin\_Inlet(UTC-05:00) Resolute(UTC-05:00) Rio\_Branco(UTC-05:00) Tell\_City(UTC-05:00) Winnipeg(UTC-04:00) Anguilla(UTC-04:00) Antigua(UTC-04:00) Aruba(UTC-04:00) Asuncion(UTC-04:00) Barbados(UTC-04:00) Blanc-Sablon(UTC-04:00) Boa\_Vista(UTC-04:00) Campo\_Grande(UTC-04:00) Caracas(UTC-04:00) Cuiaba(UTC-04:00) Curacao(UTC-04:00) Detroit(UTC-04:00) Dominica(UTC-04:00) Grand\_Turk(UTC-04:00) Grenada(UTC-04:00) Guadeloupe(UTC-04:00) Guyana(UTC-04:00) Havana(UTC-04:00) Indianapolis(UTC-04:00) Iqaluit(UTC-04:00) Kralendijk(UTC-04:00) La\_Paz(UTC-04:00) Louisville(UTC-04:00) Lower\_Princes(UTC-04:00) Manaus(UTC-04:00) Marengo(UTC-04:00) Marigot(UTC-04:00) Martinique(UTC-04:00) Monticello(UTC-04:00) Montserrat(UTC-04:00) Nassau(UTC-04:00) New\_York(UTC-04:00) Nipigon(UTC-04:00) Pangnirtung(UTC-04:00) Petersburg(UTC-04:00) Port-au-Prince(UTC-04:00) Port\_of\_Spain(UTC-04:00) Porto\_Velho(UTC-04:00) Puerto\_Rico(UTC-04:00) Santiago(UTC-04:00) Santo\_Domingo(UTC-04:00) St\_Barthelemy(UTC-04:00) St\_Kitts(UTC-04:00) St\_Lucia(UTC-04:00) St\_Thomas(UTC-04:00) St\_Vincent(UTC-04:00) Thunder\_Bay(UTC-04:00) Toronto(UTC-04:00) Tortola(UTC-04:00) Vevay(UTC-04:00) Vincennes(UTC-04:00) Winamac(UTC-03:00) Araguaina(UTC-03:00) Bahia(UTC-03:00) Belem(UTC-03:00) Bermuda(UTC-03:00) Buenos\_Aires(UTC-03:00) Catamarca(UTC-03:00) Cayenne(UTC-02:30) St\_Johns(UTC-03:00) Cordoba(UTC-03:00) Fortaleza(UTC-03:00) Glace\_Bay(UTC-03:00) Goose\_Bay(UTC-03:00) Halifax(UTC-03:00) Jujuy(UTC-03:00) La\_Rioja(UTC-03:00) Maceio(UTC-03:00) Mendoza(UTC-03:00) Moncton(UTC-03:00) Montevideo(UTC-03:00) Palmer(UTC-03:00) Paramaribo(UTC-03:00) Punta\_Arenas(UTC-03:00) Recife(UTC-03:00) Rio\_Gallegos(UTC-03:00) Rothera(UTC-03:00) Salta(UTC-03:00) San\_Juan(UTC-03:00) San\_Luis(UTC-03:00) Santarem(UTC-03:00) Sao\_Paulo(UTC-03:00) Stanley(UTC-03:00) Thule(UTC-03:00) Tucuman(UTC-03:00) Ushuaia(UTC-02:00) Miquelon(UTC-02:00) Noronha(UTC-02:00) Nuuk(UTC-02:00) South\_Georgia(UTC-01:00) Cape\_Verde(UTC+00:00) Abidjan(UTC+00:00) Accra(UTC+00:00) Azores(UTC+00:00) Bamako(UTC+00:00) Banjul(UTC+00:00) Bissau(UTC+00:00) Conakry(UTC+00:00) Dakar(UTC+00:00) Danmarkshavn(UTC+00:00) Freetown(UTC+00:00) Lome(UTC+00:00) Monrovia(UTC+00:00) Nouakchott(UTC+00:00) Ouagadougou(UTC+00:00) Reykjavik(UTC+00:00) Sao\_Tome(UTC+00:00) Scoresbysund(UTC+00:00) St\_Helena(UTC+00:00) UTC(UTC+01:00) Algiers(UTC+01:00) Bangui(UTC+01:00) Brazzaville(UTC+01:00) Canary(UTC+01:00) Casablanca(UTC+01:00) Douala(UTC+01:00) Dublin(UTC+01:00) El\_Aaiun(UTC+01:00) Faroe(UTC+01:00) Guernsey(UTC+01:00) Isle\_of\_Man(UTC+01:00) Jersey(UTC+01:00) Kinshasa(UTC+01:00) Lagos(UTC+01:00) Libreville(UTC+01:00) Lisbon(UTC+01:00) London(UTC+01:00) Luanda(UTC+01:00) Madeira(UTC+01:00) Malabo(UTC+01:00) Ndjamena(UTC+01:00) Niamey(UTC+01:00) Porto-Novo(UTC+01:00) Tunis(UTC+02:00) Amsterdam(UTC+02:00) Andorra(UTC+02:00) Belgrade(UTC+02:00) Berlin(UTC+02:00) Blantyre(UTC+02:00) Bratislava(UTC+02:00) Brussels(UTC+02:00) Budapest(UTC+02:00) Bujumbura(UTC+02:00) Busingen(UTC+02:00) Cairo(UTC+02:00) Ceuta(UTC+02:00) Copenhagen(UTC+02:00) Gaborone(UTC+02:00) Gibraltar(UTC+02:00) Harare(UTC+02:00) Johannesburg(UTC+02:00) Juba(UTC+02:00) Kaliningrad(UTC+02:00) Khartoum(UTC+02:00) Kigali(UTC+02:00) Ljubljana(UTC+02:00) Longyearbyen(UTC+02:00) Lubumbashi(UTC+02:00) Lusaka(UTC+02:00) Luxembourg(UTC+02:00) Madrid(UTC+02:00) Malta(UTC+02:00) Maputo(UTC+02:00) Maseru(UTC+02:00) Mbabane(UTC+02:00) Monaco(UTC+02:00) Oslo(UTC+02:00) Paris(UTC+02:00) Podgorica(UTC+02:00) Prague(UTC+02:00) Rome(UTC+02:00) San\_Marino(UTC+02:00) Sarajevo(UTC+02:00) Skopje(UTC+02:00) Stockholm(UTC+02:00) Tirane(UTC+02:00) Tripoli(UTC+02:00) Troll(UTC+02:00) Vaduz(UTC+02:00) Vatican(UTC+02:00) Vienna(UTC+02:00) Warsaw(UTC+02:00) Windhoek(UTC+02:00) Zagreb(UTC+02:00) Zurich(UTC+03:00) Addis\_Ababa(UTC+03:00) Aden(UTC+03:00) Amman(UTC+03:00) Antananarivo(UTC+03:00) Asmara(UTC+03:00) Athens(UTC+03:00) Baghdad(UTC+03:00) Bahrain(UTC+03:00) Beirut(UTC+03:00) Bucharest(UTC+03:00) Chisinau(UTC+03:00) Comoro(UTC+03:00) Damascus(UTC+03:00) Dar\_es\_Salaam(UTC+03:00) Djibouti(UTC+03:00) Famagusta(UTC+03:00) Gaza(UTC+03:00) Hebron(UTC+03:00) Helsinki(UTC+03:00) Istanbul(UTC+03:00) Jerusalem(UTC+03:00) Kampala(UTC+03:00) Kiev(UTC+03:00) Kirov(UTC+03:00) Kuwait(UTC+03:00) Mariehamn(UTC+03:00) Mayotte(UTC+03:00) Minsk(UTC+03:00) Mogadishu(UTC+03:00) Moscow(UTC+03:00) Nairobi(UTC+03:00) Nicosia(UTC+03:00) Qatar(UTC+03:00) Riga(UTC+03:00) Riyadh(UTC+03:00) Simferopol(UTC+03:00) Sofia(UTC+03:00) Syowa(UTC+03:00) Tallinn(UTC+03:00) Uzhgorod(UTC+03:00) Vilnius(UTC+03:00) Volgograd(UTC+03:00) Zaporozhye(UTC+04:00) Astrakhan(UTC+04:00) Baku(UTC+04:00) Dubai(UTC+04:00) Mahe(UTC+04:00) Mauritius(UTC+04:00) Muscat(UTC+04:00) Reunion(UTC+04:00) Samara(UTC+04:00) Saratov(UTC+04:00) Tbilisi(UTC+04:00) Ulyanovsk(UTC+04:00) Yerevan(UTC+05:00) Aqtau(UTC+05:00) Ashgabat(UTC+05:00) Atyrau(UTC+04:30) Kabul(UTC+05:00) Dushanbe(UTC+05:00) Kerguelen(UTC+05:00) Maldives(UTC+05:30) Colombo(UTC+05:00) Karachi(UTC+04:30) Tehran(UTC+05:30) Kolkata(UTC+05:00) Aqtobe(UTC+05:00) Mawson(UTC+05:00) Oral(UTC+05:00) Qyzylorda(UTC+05:00) Samarkand(UTC+05:00) Tashkent(UTC+05:00) Yekaterinburg(UTC+06:00) Bishkek(UTC+06:00) Chagos(UTC+06:00) Dhaka(UTC+06:00) Thimphu(UTC+07:00) Bangkok(UTC+07:00) Barnaul(UTC+07:00) Christmas(UTC+07:00) Davis(UTC+07:00) Ho\_Chi\_Minh(UTC+06:30) Cocos(UTC+06:00) Vostok(UTC+06:30) Yangon(UTC+06:00) Almaty(UTC+06:00) Omsk(UTC+06:00) Qostanay(UTC+06:00) Urumqi(UTC+05:45) Kathmandu(UTC+07:00) Hovd(UTC+07:00) Jakarta(UTC+07:00) Krasnoyarsk(UTC+07:00) Novokuznetsk(UTC+07:00) Novosibirsk(UTC+07:00) Phnom\_Penh(UTC+07:00) Pontianak(UTC+07:00) Tomsk(UTC+07:00) Vientiane(UTC+08:00) Brunei(UTC+08:00) Choibalsan(UTC+08:00) Hong\_Kong(UTC+08:00) Irkutsk(UTC+08:45) Eucla(UTC+08:00) Kuala\_Lumpur(UTC+08:00) Kuching(UTC+08:00) Macau(UTC+08:00) Makassar(UTC+08:00) Manila(UTC+08:00) Perth(UTC+08:00) Shanghai(UTC+08:00) Singapore(UTC+08:00) Taipei(UTC+08:00) Ulaanbaatar(UTC+09:00) Chita(UTC+09:30) Adelaide(UTC+09:30) Broken\_Hill(UTC+09:30) Darwin(UTC+09:00) Dili(UTC+09:00) Jayapura(UTC+09:00) Khandyga(UTC+09:00) Palau(UTC+09:00) Pyongyang(UTC+09:00) Seoul(UTC+09:00) Tokyo(UTC+09:00) Yakutsk(UTC+10:00) Brisbane(UTC+10:00) Chuuk(UTC+10:00) DumontDUrville(UTC+10:00) Guam(UTC+10:00) Hobart(UTC+10:00) Lindeman(UTC+10:00) Macquarie(UTC+10:00) Melbourne(UTC+10:00) Port\_Moresby(UTC+10:00) Saipan(UTC+10:00) Sydney(UTC+10:00) Ust-Nera(UTC+10:00) Vladivostok(UTC+11:00) Bougainville(UTC+11:00) Casey(UTC+11:00) Efate(UTC+11:00) Guadalcanal(UTC+11:00) Kosrae(UTC+11:00) Norfolk(UTC+11:00) Noumea(UTC+10:30) Lord\_Howe(UTC+11:00) Magadan(UTC+11:00) Pohnpei(UTC+11:00) Sakhalin(UTC+11:00) Srednekolymsk(UTC+12:00) Anadyr(UTC+12:00) Auckland(UTC+12:00) Fiji(UTC+12:00) Funafuti(UTC+12:00) Kamchatka(UTC+12:00) Nauru(UTC+13:00) Apia(UTC+12:45) Chatham(UTC+12:00) Kwajalein(UTC+12:00) Majuro(UTC+12:00) McMurdo(UTC+12:00) Tarawa(UTC+12:00) Wake(UTC+12:00) Wallis(UTC+13:00) Fakaofo(UTC+13:00) Kanton(UTC+13:00) Tongatapu(UTC+14:00) Kiritimati

This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms?hl=en) apply.

I agree to the processing of my personal data by REVAS Sp. z o.o. based in Rzeszów to contact me at my request in accordance with the [Privacy Policy](https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy/). I know that consent is voluntary.\*

×

Did you like what you saw?

Send us a message

You can leave a short note to contact you or, if you want, describe your question in details

Name and surname\*

E-mail\*

Message

This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms?hl=en) apply.

I agree to the processing of my personal data by REVAS Sp. z o.o. based in Rzeszów to contact me at my request in accordance with the [Privacy Policy](https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy/). I know that consent is voluntary.\*

×

Name and surname\*

E-mail\*

Message

This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms?hl=en) apply.

I agree to the processing of my personal data by REVAS Sp. z o.o. based in Rzeszów to contact me at my request in accordance with the [Privacy Policy](https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy/). I know that consent is voluntary.\*

X

Did you like what you saw?

Leave us your details

And we will call you back as soon as possible

Phone number

\* I agree to the processing of my personal data by REVAS Sp. z o.o. based in Rzeszów to contact me at my request in accordance with [Privacy Policy](https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy/).

×

The Revas software flexible solutions, possible combinations and a well-chosen method of analyzing the output data, for which the game participant is responsible, indicate that this tool should be more widely used not only in secondary education, but above all in universities, where each participant, even tangibly will be able to observe what are the effects of business operations of virtual companies.  
I have seen many similar solutions, but the quality of REVAS software should be a specific reference as a great example of product accuracy.

Piotr Zawada Associate Professor

Lecturer  
Cardinal Stefan Wyszyński University in Warsaw

×

Datenschutzerklärung

Die Firma Revas bedankt sich für Ihren Besuch auf unserer Website und Ihr Interesse an unserem Unternehmen und unseren Leistungen. Der Schutz Ihrer Privatsphäre bei der Verarbeitung ist für uns ein wichtiges Anliegen. Deshalb werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nur gemäß den Bestimmungen des deutschen Datenschutzrechts verarbeitet. Wir möchten, dass Sie sich beim Besuch unserer Internetseiten sicher fühlen.

**Personenbezogene Daten**

Personenbezogene Daten sind Einzelangaben über persönliche oder sachliche Verhältnisse einer bestimmten oder bestimmbaren natürlichen Person. Darunter fallen Informationen wie z.B. Name, Anschrift, E-Mail und Telefonnummer. Die rechtlichen Grundlagen des Datenschutzes finden Sie im Bundesdatenschutzgesetz (BDSG), der EU-Datenschutzgrundverordnung (EU-DSGVO, ab 25.05.2018) und dem Telemediengesetz (TMG).

Die Nutzung unserer Seite ist i.d.R. ohne eine Angabe von personenbezogenen Daten möglich. Für die Nutzung einzelner Services unserer Seite können sich hierfür abweichende Regelungen ergeben, die in diesem Falle nachstehend gesondert erläutert werden und Sie insbesondere über Art, Umfang und Zweck der Erhebung, die Nutzung und die Verarbeitung von personenbezogenen Daten informieren.

**Cookies**

Unsere Website nutzt so genannte Cookies, welche dazu dienen, unsere Internetpräsenz insgesamt nutzerfreundlicher, effektiver sowie sicherer zu machen – etwa wenn es darum geht, das Navigieren auf unserer Plattform zu beschleunigen. Zudem versetzen uns Cookies in die Lage, etwa die Häufigkeit von Seitenaufrufen und die allgemeine Navigation zu messen.

Bei Cookies handelt es sich um kleine Textdateien, die auf Ihrem Computersystem abgelegt werden. Cookies richten auf Ihrem Rechner keinen Schaden an und enthalten keine Viren. Wir weisen Sie darauf hin, dass einige dieser Cookies von unserem Server auf Ihr Computersystem überspielt werden, wobei es sich dabei meist um so genannte “Session –Cookies ” handelt. „Session-Cookies“ zeichnen sich dadurch aus, dass diese automatisch nach Ende der Browser-Sitzung wieder von Ihrer Festplatte gelöscht werden. Andere Cookies verbleiben auf Ihrem Computersystem und ermöglichen es uns, Ihr Computersystem bei Ihrem nächsten Besuch wieder zu erkennen (sog. dauerhafte Cookies). Selbstverständlich können Sie Cookies jederzeit ablehnen, sofern Ihr Browser dies zulässt. Wir weisen Sie jedoch darauf hin, dass Sie in diesem Fall gegebenenfalls nicht sämtliche Funktionen unserer Website vollumfänglich nutzen können.

Die Hilfe-Funktion in der Menüleiste der meisten Webbrowser erklärt Ihnen, wie Sie Ihren Browser davon abhalten, neue Cookies zu akzeptieren, wie Sie Ihren Browser darauf hinweisen lassen, wenn Sie ein neues Cookie erhalten oder auch wie Sie sämtliche erhaltenen Cookies ausschalten. Ähnliche Funktionen wie Flash Cookies, die durch Browser-Add-ons genutzt werden, können Sie durch die Änderung der Einstellungen des Browser-Add-on oder auch über die Website des Herstellers des Browser Add-on ausschalten oder löschen.

**Einsatz eines Kontaktformulars**

Wenn Sie uns per Kontaktformular Anfragen zukommen lassen, werden Ihre Angaben aus dem Anfrageformular inklusive der von Ihnen dort angegebenen Kontaktdaten zwecks Bearbeitung der Anfrage und für den Fall von Anschlussfragen bei uns gespeichert. Diese Daten geben wir nicht ohne Ihre Einwilligung weiter.

**Aktive Komponenten**

Auf unseren Webseiten werden keine aktiven Komponenten wie Java-Applets oder Active-X-Controls verwendet.

**Kontaktmöglichkeit**

Wir bieten Ihnen auf unserer Webseite die Möglichkeit, mit uns per E-Mail und/oder über Kontaktformulare in Verbindung zu treten. Ihre Angaben aus dem Anfrageformular inklusive der von Ihnen dort angegebenen Kontaktdaten zwecks Bearbeitung der Anfrage und für den Fall von Anschlussfragen werden dann verschlüsselt an uns weitergeleitet und bei uns gespeichert. Eine Weitergabe an Dritte erfolgt nicht.

**Einsatz von Google-Analytics mit Anonymisierungsfunktion**

Diese Website nutzt Funktionen des Webanalysedienstes Google Analytics. Anbieter ist die Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Google Analytics verwendet so genannte “Cookies”. Das sind Textdateien, die auf Ihrem Computer gespeichert werden und die eine Analyse der Benutzung der Website durch Sie ermöglichen. Die durch den Cookie erzeugten Informationen über Ihre Benutzung dieser Website werden in der Regel an einen Server von Google in den USA übertragen und dort gespeichert.

Mehr Informationen zum Umgang mit Nutzerdaten bei Google Analytics finden Sie in der Datenschutzerklärung von Google: [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=de](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=de)

**Browser Plugin**

Sie können die Speicherung der Cookies durch eine entsprechende Einstellung Ihrer Browser-Software verhindern; wir weisen Sie jedoch darauf hin, dass Sie in diesem Fall gegebenenfalls nicht sämtliche Funktionen dieser Website vollumfänglich werden nutzen können. Sie können darüber hinaus die Erfassung der durch den Cookie erzeugten und auf Ihre Nutzung der Website bezogenen Daten (inkl. Ihrer IP-Adresse) an Google sowie die Verarbeitung dieser Daten durch Google verhindern, indem Sie das unter dem folgenden Link verfügbare Browser-Plugin herunterladen und installieren: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de)

**Widerspruch gegen Datenerfassung**

Sie können die Erfassung Ihrer Daten durch Google Analytics verhindern, indem Sie auf folgenden Link klicken. Es wird ein Opt-Out-Cookie gesetzt, der die Erfassung Ihrer Daten bei zukünftigen Besuchen dieser Website verhindert: Google Analytics deaktivieren. [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de)

**IP-Anonymisierung**

Wir nutzen die Funktion “Aktivierung der IP-Anonymisierung” auf dieser Webseite. Dadurch wird Ihre IP-Adresse von Google jedoch innerhalb von Mitgliedstaaten der Europäischen Union oder in anderen Vertragsstaaten des Abkommens über den Europäischen Wirtschaftsraum zuvor gekürzt. Nur in Ausnahmefällen wird die volle IP-Adresse an einen Server von Google in den USA übertragen und dort gekürzt. Im Auftrag des Betreibers dieser Website wird Google diese Informationen benutzen, um Ihre Nutzung der Website auszuwerten, um Reports über die Websiteaktivitäten zusammenzustellen und um weitere mit der Websitenutzung und der Internetnutzung verbundene Dienstleistungen gegenüber dem Websitebetreiber zu erbringen. Die im Rahmen von Google Analytics von Ihrem Browser übermittelte IP-Adresse wird nicht mit anderen Daten von Google zusammengeführt.

**Einsatz von Google-Maps**

Diese Website nutzt die Komponente “Google Maps” zur Darstellung von Lageplänen, betrieben von der Firma Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, nachfolgend „Google“.

Bei jedem Aufruf der Komponente “Google Maps” wird von Google ein Cookie gesetzt, um bei der Anzeige der Seite, auf der die Komponente “Google Maps” integriert ist, Nutzereinstellungen und -daten zu verarbeiten. Dieses Cookie wird im Regelfall nicht durch das Schließen des Browsers gelöscht, sondern läuft nach einer bestimmten Zeit ab, soweit es nicht von Ihnen zuvor manuell gelöscht wird.

Wenn Sie mit dieser Verarbeitung Ihrer Daten nicht einverstanden sind, so besteht die Möglichkeit, den Service von “Google Maps” zu deaktivieren und auf diesem Weg die Übertragung von Daten an Google zu verhindern. Dazu müssen Sie die Java-Script-Funktion in Ihrem Browser deaktivieren. Wir weisen Sie jedoch darauf hin, dass Sie in diesem Fall die “Google Maps” nicht oder nur eingeschränkt nutzen können.

Die Nutzung von “Google Maps” und der über “Google Maps” erlangten Informationen erfolgt gemäß den Google-Nutzungsbedingungen http://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/terms/regional.html sowie der zusätzlichen Geschäftsbedingungen für „Google Maps“ https://www.google.com/intl/de\_de/help/terms\_maps.html.

**Einsatz von Google Tag Manager**

Diese Webseite verwendet den Google Tag Manager. Durch diesen Dienst können Website-Tags über eine Oberfläche verwaltet werden. Der Google Tag Manager implementiert lediglich Tags. Das bedeutet: Es werden keine Cookies eingesetzt und es werden keine personenbezogenen Daten erfasst. Der Google Tool Manager löst andere Tags aus, die wiederum ggf. Daten erfassen. Jedoch greift der Google Tag Manager nicht auf diese Daten zu. Wurde auf Domain- oder Cookie-Ebene eine Deaktivierung vorgenommen, so bleibt sie für alle Tracking-Tags bestehen, insofern diese mit dem Google Tag Manager implementiert werden.

**Einsatz von Youtube**

Unsere Webseite setzt Komponenten der von Google betriebenen Seite Youtube ein. Betreiber der Seiten ist die Youtube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA.

Wir nutzen die von Youtube zur Verfügung gestellte Option ” erweiterter Datenschutzmodus”.

Sobald Sie eine Seite unserer Internetpräsenz besuchen, auf der Videos eingebettet sind, wird eine Verbindung zu den Servern von Youtube aufgebaut. Laut Angaben von Youtube wird dem Youtube-Server mitgeteilt, welche spezielle Seite unserer Internetpräsenz von Ihnen besucht wurde, wenn Sie ein Video anschauen. Sollten Sie obendrein in Ihrem Youtube-Account eingeloggt sein, ermöglichen Sie es Youtube, Ihr Surfverhalten direkt Ihrem persönlichen Profil zuzuordnen. Sie können dieser Möglichkeit der Zuordnung vorbeugen, indem Sie sich vorher aus Ihrem Account ausloggen.

Weitere Informationen zur Erhebung und Nutzung Ihrer Daten durch Youtube erhalten Sie in den Hinweisen zum Datenschutz unter https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy/.

**Einsatz von Google-AdWords**

Wir setzen zur Bewerbung unserer Website ferner das Google Werbetool “Google-Adwords” ein. Im Rahmen dessen verwenden wir auf unserer Website den Analysedienst “Conversion-Tracking” der Firma Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, nachfolgend „Google“. Sofern Sie über eine Google-Anzeige auf unsere Webseite gelangt sind, wird ein Cookie auf Ihrem Rechner abgelegt. Cookies sind kleine Textdateien, die Ihr Internet-Browser auf Ihrem Rechner ablegt und speichert. Diese sog. “Conversion- Cookies” verlieren nach 30 Tagen ihre Gültigkeit und dienen nicht Ihrer persönlichen Identifikation. Besuchen Sie bestimmte Seiten unserer Website und das Cookie ist noch nicht abgelaufen, können wir und Google erkennen, dass Sie als Nutzer auf eine unserer bei Google platzierten Anzeigen geklickt haben und zu unserer Seite weitergeleitet wurden.Die mit Hilfe der “Conversion-Cookies” eingeholten Informationen dienen Google dazu, Besuchs-Statistiken für unsere Website zu erstellen. Wir erfahren durch diese Statistik die Gesamtanzahl der Nutzer, die auf unsere Anzeige geklickt haben und zudem welche Seiten unserer Website vom jeweiligen Nutzer im Anschluss aufgerufen wurden. Wir bzw. andere über “Google-Adwords” Werbende erhalten jedoch keinerlei Informationen, mit denen sich Nutzer persönlich identifizieren lassen. Sie können die Installation der “Conversion-Cookies” durch eine entsprechende Einstellung Ihres Browsers verhindern, etwa per Browser-Einstellung, die das automatische Setzen von Cookies generell deaktiviert oder speziell nur die Cookies von der Domain “googleadservices.com“ blockiert. Die diesbezügliche Datenschutzerklärung von Google erhalten Sie unter nachfolgendem Link: https://services.google.com/sitestats/de.html.

**Einsatz von Google Remarketing**

Wir setzen auf unserer Website den Dienst Google Remarketing der Firma Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, nachfolgend „Google“ ein. Mit Google-Remarketing können Anzeigen für Nutzer geschaltet werden, die unsere Webseite in der Vergangenheit bereits besucht haben. Innerhalb des Google-Werbenetzwerks können hierdurch an ihre Interessen angepasste Werbeanzeigen auf unserer Seite dargestellt werden. Google-Remarketing verwendet für diese Auswertung Cookies. Cookies sind kleine Textdateien, die auf Ihrem Computer gespeichert werden und die eine Analyse der Benutzung der Webseite ermöglicht. Hierdurch wird es ermöglicht, unsere Besucher wiederzuerkennen, sobald diese Webseiten innerhalb des Werbenetzwerks von Google aufrufen. Auf diese Weise können innerhalb des Werbenetzwerks von Google Werbeanzeigen präsentiert werden, die auf Inhalte bezogen sind, die der Besucher zuvor auf Webseiten des Werbenetzwerks von Google aufgerufen hat, die ebenfalls die Remarketing Funktion von Google verwenden. Google erhebt hierbei nach eigenen Angaben keine personenbezogenen Daten. Sie können diese Funktion deaktivieren, wenn Sie unter http://www.google.com/settings/ads die entsprechenden Einstellungen vornehmen.

**Einsatz von WiredMinds**

Zu Zwecken des Marketings und der Optimierung werden auf unserer Website Produkte und Dienstleistungen der WiredMinds AG verwendet. Dabei werden Daten erhoben, verarbeitet und gespeichert, aus denen unter einem Pseudonym Nutzungsprofile erstellt werden. Hierzu können Cookies zum Einsatz kommen. Die erhobenen Daten, die auch personenbezogene Daten beinhalten können, werden an WiredMinds übermittelt oder direkt von WiredMinds erhoben. WiredMinds darf Informationen, die durch Besuche auf den Websites hinterlassen werden, nutzen um anonymisierte Nutzungsprofile zu erstellen. Die dabei gewonnenen Daten werden ohne die gesondert erteilte Zustimmung des Betroffenen nicht benutzt, um den Besucher dieser Website persönlich zu identifizieren und sie werden nicht mit personenbezogenen Daten über den Träger des Pseudonyms zusammengeführt. Soweit IP-Adressen erhoben werden, werden diese unverzüglich nach Erhebung durch Löschen des letzten Nummernblocks anonymisiert.

**Nutzung und Weitergabe personenbezogener Daten**

Wenn Sie uns mit der Erbringung einer Leistung beauftragen, werden Ihre personenbezogenen Daten nur insoweit verwendet, wie es für die Erbringung die Durchführung des Auftrages notwendig ist (z.B. zur Bearbeitung von Informationsanfragen oder Prospektbestellungen). Hierzu zählt insbesondere die Weitergabe Ihrer Daten an die für Ihre Anfrage zuständigen Partner aus der Revas Partnergemeinschaft, an Transportunternehmen, Kreditunternehmen oder andere zur Erbringung der Dienstleistung oder Vertragsabwicklung eingesetzten Service-Dienste.

Eine darüberhinausgehende Weitergabe, insbesondere ein Verkauf Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten an Dritte erfolgt nicht.

Außer: Wir geben Kundenkonten und persönliche Daten über Kunden bekannt, wenn wir hierzu gesetzlich verpflichtet sind oder wenn eine solche Weitergabe erforderlich ist, um unsere allgemeinen Geschäftsbedingungen oder andere Vereinbarungen durchzusetzen oder unsere Rechte sowie die Rechte unserer Kunden und diejenigen Dritter zu schützen, z.B. im Fall von Angriffen auf unsere Netzinfrastruktur zur Rechts- oder Strafverfolgung. Dies beinhaltet einen Datenaustausch mit Unternehmen, die auf die Vorbeugung und Minimierung von Missbrauch und Kreditkartenbetrug spezialisiert sind. Es wird ausdrücklich klargestellt, dass in diesem Zusammenhang keine Weitergabe der Daten an diese Unternehmen zum wirtschaftlichen Gebrauch erfolgt, der im Widerspruch zu dieser Datenschutzerklärung steht.

**Verpflichtung der Mitarbeiter und externen Dienstleistern**

Selbstverständlich sind unsere Mitarbeiter und die von uns beauftragten Dienstleistungsunternehmen zur Verschwiegenheit und zur Einhaltung der Bestimmungen des Bundesdatenschutzgesetzes verpflichtet.

**Zweckbezogene Nutzung der personenbezogenen Daten**

Jegliche Nutzung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten erfolgt nur zu den genannten Zwecken und in dem zur Erreichung dieser Zwecke erforderlichen Umfang.

**Zusammenarbeit mit externen Dienstleistern**

Wir beauftragen andere Unternehmen und Einzelpersonen mit der Erfüllung von Aufgaben für uns. Beispiele sind u. a. Paketlieferung, Sendung von Briefen oder E-Mails, die Pflege unserer Kundenlisten, die Analyse unserer Datenbanken, Werbemaßnahmen (einschließlich der Zur-Verfügung-Stellung von Suchergebnissen und Links), Abwicklung von Zahlungen (Kreditkarte, Lastschriftverfahren und Rechnungskauf) sowie Kundenservice. Diese Dienstleister haben Zugang zu persönlichen Informationen, die zur Erfüllung ihrer Aufgaben benötigt werden. Sie dürfen diese jedoch nicht zu anderen Zwecken verwenden. Darüber hinaus sind sie verpflichtet, die Informationen gemäß dieser Datenschutzerklärung sowie den deutschen Datenschutzgesetzen zu behandeln.

Falls es sich bei diesen Subunternehmen um Auftragsdatenverarbeiter gemäß § 11 BDSG (Auftragsverarbeiter gemäß Artikel 28 EU-DSGVO) handelt, haben wir mit diesen entsprechende gesetzeskonformen Verträgen geschlossen.

**Informationssicherheit**

Die Firma Revas setzt technische und organisatorische Sicherheitsmaßnahmen nach dem derzeitigen Wissensstand ein, um Ihre uns zur Verfügung gestellten Daten durch zufällige oder vorsätzliche Manipulation, Verlust, Zerstörung oder den Zugriff unberechtigter Personen zu schützen. So werden Ihre Daten in einer sicheren Betriebsumgebung gespeichert, die der Öffentlichkeit nicht zugänglich ist. Unsere Sicherheitsmaßnahmen werden in regelmäßigen Abständen überprüft und entsprechend der technologischen Entwicklung fortlaufend verbessert.

Sollten Sie mit uns per E-Mail in Kontakt treten wollen, weisen wir darauf hin, dass die Vertraulichkeit der übermittelten Informationen bei unverschlüsselten E-Mails nicht gewährleistet ist. Der Inhalt von unverschlüsselten E-Mails kann von Dritten eingesehen werden. Wir empfehlen Ihnen daher, uns vertrauliche Informationen entweder verschlüsselt oder über den Postweg zukommen zu lassen.

Ihre E-Mail-Adresse wird ausschließlich für die Korrespondenz mit Ihnen verwendet. Eine anderweitige Nutzung oder Weitergabe an Dritte erfolgt nicht.

**Schutz Ihrer Daten durch TLS bzw. SSL**

Zur sicheren Datenübertragung im Internet benutzen wir das hybride Verschlüsselungsprotokoll Transport Layer Security (TLS, deutsch Transportschichtsicherheit), weitläufiger bekannt unter der Vorgängerbezeichnung Secure Sockets Layer Software (SSL). Diese Software verschlüsselt die Informationen, die von Ihnen übermittelt werden. Alle datenschutzrelevanten Informationen (wie Name, Adresse, Kreditkartennummer, Bankleitzahl, Bankkontonummer, …) werden in verschlüsselter Form in einer geschützten Datenbank abgelegt.

**Auskunft, Löschung, Sperrung**

Sie haben jederzeit das Recht auf unentgeltliche Auskunft über Ihre gespeicherten personenbezogenen Daten, deren Herkunft und Empfänger und den Zweck der Datenverarbeitung – ohne Angabe von Gründen. Ebenso haben Sie ein Recht auf Berichtigung, Sperrung oder Löschung dieser Daten.

Hierzu sowie zu weiteren Fragen zum Thema Datenschutz / personenbezogene Daten können Sie sich jederzeit an uns wenden:

* per Post an Revas sp. z o.o., Popieluszki 26C, 35-328 Rzeszow, Poland
* per E-Mail an: info@revas.online

**Einwilligung, Stand und Änderung dieser Datenschutzerklärung**

Mit der Nutzung unserer Webseite willigen Sie in die vorab beschriebene Datenverwendung ein. Derzeitiger Stand ist März 2019.

Wir behalten uns das Recht vor, diese Datenschutzerklärung jederzeit unter Beachtung der geltenden Datenschutzvorschriften mit Wirkung für die Zukunft zu ändern. Die Änderungen werden wir an dieser Stelle veröffentlichen.

x

Privacy policy

By using the website service, you entrust us with your information. This Privacy Policy serves to help you understand what data we collect, for what purpose and what we use it for. This information is important, so please read this document carefully.

**Collection and processing of users’ personal data**

Data about users of the website [https://www.revas.online/en/](https://www.revas.online/en/) are processed by REVAS spółka z ograniczoną odpowiedzialnością (limited liability company) with registered head office in Rzeszów (address: Popiełuszki 26C, 35-328 Rzeszów) entered into the Register of Companies of the National Court Register maintained by the District Court in Rzeszów, 12th Commercial Division of the National Court Register under KRS number 0000638640, with the following NIP: 5170376971 and REGON identification number: 365460300, with share capital in the amount of PLN 5,000.

**Information provided by the user when creating an account on the website:**  
In order to fully use the services offered by the website, it is recommended to register. In such cases, you are kindly requested to provide personal details in the form, such as your name and e-mail address. We will store them with your account details. The information provided in the form is used by us for necessary contacts with our users and in order to better adapt the content and advertising that we present to their needs and interests. Demographic data (e.g. age, gender, size of city) can also be combined with selected operational data (e.g. saved in cookie files) and used to test user preferences and improve the quality of the services we provide.  
The set of collected personal data of users is treated as a separate database stored on the server in a special security zone ensuring proper protection. Only a small number of authorized people who deal with the administration of the database have full access to the database.  
We provide each user, who has completed the registration form or otherwise provided his personal data to us, with access to their data, for the purposes of verification, modification or deletion. Providing personal data is voluntary.  
The collected personal data is not sold or lent to other persons or institutions, unless it is done with the express permission or at the request of the user or at the request of the lawful state authorities for the purposes of their proceedings. We may, however, disclose aggregate, general statistical summaries, that we have produced, to websites or advertising agencies cooperating with us. Such listings may refer mainly to the viewership of our websites and do not contain data allowing identification of individual users.

**How we use the information obtained:**

**Providing, improving and developing our services.**  
The availability of this information allows us to maintain the Services, personalize the content and suggest different solutions to users, because it is thanks to the information collected that we understand how users use elements of the Services and resources that are of interest to them. We also use the information we collect to offer various facilities and suggestions.

**Communication with the**  
We use information about the User in choosing the marketing content to be sent, in communication about services and in order to inform about our policies and regulations. We also use it to respond to your requests for contact.

**View monitoring of ads and services**  
We use the information we have available to improve our advertising and measurement systems, which in turn is intended to display ads that interest the user both within and outside the website, as well as to measure the effectiveness and reach – of both ads and services.  
We provide and support our Services using cookies and other similar technologies, applying them in each of the areas described here using information about users.

**Policy for cookies and other similar technologies**

In connection with providing the content of websites, we use so-called cookies, i.e. information saved by servers on the user’s terminal device, which servers can read every time they connect to this terminal device. We may also use other technologies with functions similar or identical to cookies. In this document, information about cookies also applies to other similar technologies used within our websites. Cookie files (or ‘cookies’) consist of IT data, in particular text files, which are stored in the user’s terminal device connected to websites. Cookies usually contain the domain name of the website they come from, the time they were stored on the terminal device and a unique number.  
Cookies are used to:  
1) adapt the content of websites to user preferences and optimize the use of websites; in particular, these files allows the recognition of the user of the website’s device and proper display of the website, tailored to his individual needs,  
2) create statistics that help to understand how the website users use the websites, which allows improvements in their structure and content,  
3) maintaining the user session of the website (after logging in), thanks to which the user does not have to re-enter their login and password on each subpage of the website,  
4) providing users with advertising content more tailored to their interests.  
As part of our websites, we may use the following types of cookies:  
1) “essential” cookies, enabling the use of services available as part of the website, e.g. authentication cookies used for services that require authentication on the site,  
2) cookies used to ensure security, e.g. used to detect fraud in the field of authentication within the website,  
3) cookies enabling the collection of information on the use of website pages,  
4) “functional” cookies that enable “remembering” the settings selected by the user and personalization of the user interface, e.g. in the scope of the selected language or region of the user’s origin, font size, website appearance, etc.,  
5) “advertising” cookies, enabling provision to the users of advertising content more tailored to their interests.  
In many cases, software used for browsing websites (web browser) allows cookies to be stored in the user’s terminal device by default. Website users can change cookie settings at any time. These settings can be changed, in particular in such a way as to block the automatic handling of cookies in the settings of the web browser or to inform the user of the website about each placing in their device. Detailed information about the possibilities and ways of using cookies is available in the software (web browser) settings. Failure to change the cookie settings means that they will be placed in the user’s terminal device, and thus we will store information on the user’s terminal device and access this information.  
Disabling the use of cookies may make it difficult to use certain services on our websites, in particular those requiring login. Disabling the option of accepting cookies does not make it impossible to read or watch content posted on websites, apart from those to which access requires login.  
Cookies can be placed on the user of the website’s terminal device, and then used by advertisers, research companies and multimedia application providers who work with us.

**Information contained in access logs**  
Like most publishers of websites, we collect information about the use of the websites by users and their IP addresses based on the analysis of access logs. This information is used for technical purposes related to the administration of the servers of our websites, as well as for statistical purposes, for the demographic analysis of users. We may be required to provide information, including in particular the computer’s IP number, included in the access logs on demand authorized by law of the state authorities for the purposes of proceedings conducted by them.

**Summonses and court orders and damages prevention**  
We reserve the right to access the user’s information, store and share it in the case of summonses and court orders, if we believe in good faith that we are obliged to do so by law. This may also apply to summonses and orders from jurisdictions from outside Poland, for which we believe in good faith that this is required by the law of the jurisdiction, applies to users in a given jurisdiction and is compliant with international standards. We also reserve the right to obtain, store and transmit information in the case of a good faith belief that this is necessary to detect frauds and other illegal activities, prevent such actions or minimise their effects, to protect us, the User and others, including in investigations, as well as to prevent risks to human life or health. We may, for example, provide other entities with information about the credibility of the user’s account, with a view to preventing fraud and abuse, both inside and outside our website. The information we collect may be displayed, processed and retained for a long period if it is subject to a court order or subpoena, investigation by law enforcement or investigation of violations of our terms or policies, or if its storage may otherwise prevent damage. We also reserve the right to store information about accounts blocked as a result of violation of our regulations for at least a year to prevent further violations and other breaches of our regulations.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

The privacy policy can be changed. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of information and will always be available at the Internet address [https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy/](https://www.revas.online/en/privacy-policy/). If we make changes to this policy, we will inform users about this fact on the website, or via e-mail to the e-mail address associated with the account. By continuing to access or use the Services after these changes take effect, the user agrees to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

x
